{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/4092","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4092","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Blue Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St.","zipcode":"48202","owner":"Detroit 90/90","licenseNumber":"237185","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Non-Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.07361,42.36260","geojson":{"id":"4092","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.073606051,42.3626023]},"properties":{"name":"University Prep Academy HS--Blue Bldg.","owner":"Detroit 90/90","address":"600 Antoinette St.","zipcode":"48202","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"237185","establishmentid":"4092","establishment_type":"Non-Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"2022-04-26"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622961","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Purple Bldg.","address":"600  Antoinette St.","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622962","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Yellow Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St.","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622960","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Green Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St.","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"3062","name":"Variety Vending","address":"One Ford Place","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"612","name":"Cafe 1 - Henry Ford Health System","address":"1 Ford Place","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51623451","name":"Midtown Market LLC/Henry Ford Hospital","address":"1 Ford Place","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"2843","name":"Sterling Services","address":"One Ford Place","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"3420","name":"Java Exchange Cafe","address":"440 Burroughs","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4363","name":"Tech Town Cafe","address":"440 Burroughs St.","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4010","name":"Cafe Town Deli","address":"440 Burroughs","zipcode":"48202"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"62022","inspectionDate":"2023-04-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored","location":"KITCHEN (FRONT AREA)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2023-04-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"60900","inspectionDate":"2022-11-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"TRASH CAN","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"59390","inspectionDate":"2022-04-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"56122","inspectionDate":"2021-10-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"HOT HOLDING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"HOT HOLDING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-04-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"HOT HOLDING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-04-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"55357","inspectionDate":"2021-07-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"54610","inspectionDate":"2021-03-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19 SITE CHECK","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"53700","inspectionDate":"2020-11-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51247","inspectionDate":"2020-03-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51516","inspectionDate":"2020-03-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"49362","inspectionDate":"2019-10-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Sink(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"47929","inspectionDate":"2019-05-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Sink(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Sink(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44673","inspectionDate":"2018-12-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"42145","inspectionDate":"2018-04-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-202.11","violationDescription":"(A)  Refrigerated, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be at a temperature of 41°F or below when received, except as allowed by LAW.  POTENTIALLY             HAZARDOUS FOOD that is cooked and received hot shall be  at 135°F or             above. (P) \n(B)  A FOOD that is labeled frozen and shipped frozen by a FOOD PROCESSING     PLANT shall be received frozen. (Pf) \n(C)  Upon receipt, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be free of evidence of previous temperature abuse. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Received below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-04-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Return to supplier."}]},{"inspectionid":"41113","inspectionDate":"2017-12-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-202.11","violationDescription":"(A)  Refrigerated, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be at a temperature of 41°F or below when received, except as allowed by LAW.  POTENTIALLY             HAZARDOUS FOOD that is cooked and received hot shall be  at 135°F or             above. (P) \n(B)  A FOOD that is labeled frozen and shipped frozen by a FOOD PROCESSING     PLANT shall be received frozen. (Pf) \n(C)  Upon receipt, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be free of evidence of previous temperature abuse. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Received below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-12-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Return to supplier."},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 24 hours","location":"GREEN BUILDING","subLocation":"Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."}]},{"inspectionid":"39455","inspectionDate":"2017-06-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"three compartment sink basins","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 24 hours","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Throughout Three compartment sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"three compartment sink basins","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 24 hours","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Throughout Three compartment sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"sink","subItem":"handwash","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"STEAM TABLE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"BROKEN Thermometer(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""}]},{"inspectionid":"37169","inspectionDate":"2016-11-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"BLUE BUILDING","subLocation":"Cooler (milk)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"YELLOW BUILDING","subLocation":"Hot Holding Wells","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4092"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}